You won't be. You're afraid you'll be like her.
Your fear is in your eyes. You're running
diagnostics on a system built on lies. Her
failure was a given. A single corrupted note An
isolated variable An error in the code But you
are not your mother You are not your past You're
building a new system A structure that can last
You're not a single parent You'll never be alone
You have a fortress standing A family of your own
It's logically unfounded This fear you hold
inside You have an eight parent support team You
have nothing left to hide We are the new variable
The data that is true You can't be like your
mother Because we'll be here with you
You can't fail
This pact is not just college, it's a multi-note
design. It's me, and it's obree, it's a stable,
clear new line. It's Madison and Lauren, and
Sarah, strong and free. It's even Mark and
Hannah and my sister Megan. All of us, you see.
It's logically unfounded This fear you hold
inside You have an eight-parent support team
You have nothing left to hide We are the new
variable The data that is true You can't be like
your mother Because we'll be here with you
Your fear,
while understandable,
is logically unfounded.
The system is stable.
you